You've got a great voice!
Oh, you really think so?
So you're um...
I'm Oozora Akari.
And I'm Manaka Laala!
Nice to meet you, Laala!
Nice to meet you too, Akari!
Today's the rebirth of a sensation
Let's make the most of it!
Something coming to life from our imagination
A one of a kind sensation
I'll become a brand-new me
and devote everything to what I love
I'll show you a present facing the future
For now and forever, our hearts will shine brighter than the sun.
Don't forget it! (Start dash!)
Today's the rebirth of a sensation
Let's make the most of it!
This is the start line!
We'll see a brand-new sky
Fun is just beyond the horizon
The start of a dream,
and the start of a miracle
Are waiting for me!
Thank you!
Thanks, everyone!
Hold the phone!
Now wait a second-pri!
Now why the heck are there two of you singing?
Wasn't this supposed to be a solo performance?!
Who's that girl next to Laala-pri?
She's an amazing singer and dancer!
This was supposed to be an Akari solo...
Who's that cute little girl next to her?
Actually, now that I'm lo around, I see a lot of unfamiliar faces...
Well, now that you mention it...
We're not really sure how it happened, either...
Ai-katsu, Ai-katsu, Ai-katsu, Ai-katsu
I'm Oozora Akari!
I'm a third year at the Starlight Academy middle school!
Our school's holding an event today,
a big idol meetup!/get-together,
Today's Starlight Academy's festival day!
Kokone, Miyabi, and Niina showed up as our special guests.
It's almsot time for the performance to start!
You're up first, Akari. Give them a performance to remember!
And you can bet we'll be cheering you on from the audience!
Thanks!
See you later!
I'm Manaka Laala!
Primary school 6th year!
Today we're having the "long time, no pri"
Parajuku Special Concert event!
Tricolore's coming to be our special guests!
It's almost concert time!
You're first up to pri today, Laala!
Being quick and decisive is the key!
Get them fired up with a great show!
Capisce!
Huh? What?
Please scan the necessary amount of PriTickets for your coord.
Wha?
Huh?
Whaaaat?!
Wh-what the heck is this place?
I dunno! I've never seen this place before!
But wait a sec, who are you?
What about you?
Are you an idol?
Hold on.
Are you an idol, too?
yeah.
Oh, yeah...
I was supposed to be putting on a concert here...
Oh, right! I was, too!
What's this?
Start Dash Sensation...
Oh! That's the song I was supposed to sing!
Really?
It's a great song!
Thank you...
Say, would you like to perform together?
Wait, really?
You bet!
Awesome!
You've got a great voice!
Oh, really?
Um...
I'm Oozora Akari!
I'm Manaka Laala!
Excited to go on with you, Laala!
Same with you, Akari!
And that's how it all happened.
We just kinda ended up singing together.
"We just kinda ended up up singing together!"
What, is this normal to you-pri?
That certainly sounds like something Akari would do.
Everyone, please remain calm.
Oh my god...
Just where in the world are we...
Headmistress Orihime, Mr. Johnny!
You lot certainly aren't Starlight Academy students.
I'm from Paprika Academy.
"Paprika"?
I never heard of any schools with that name.
This is PriPara, isn't it?
"PriPara"?
Huh? You've never heard of it?
PriPara is an idol theme park where any girl can be an idol!
When we enter with our PriTickets, everyone becomes an idol!
Any girl can be an idol!
An idol park called PriPara?
Mm! How [fresh? idk]
But I guess you guys can perform without going to PriPara, right?
How does that work?
Well, Starlight Academy is dedicated to [raising?] idols
so we take lessons, go on the Starlight Stage,
and sometimes we get to do idol work outside school.
Those are our idol activities, aka idol katsudou!
We call them "Aikatsu"!
"Idol katsudou"; Aikatsu for short!
A school dedicated to idoling...
So you guys have a school that's just about idols?
That sounds so banger!
We have to keep up with our regular studies, too.
Really...
PriPara and Starlight Academy...
Two places have become one...
But why?
I believe that's something I can explain.
Who might you be?
I'm Meganii, PriPara's operator.
I'm Meganee, PriPara's other operator.
You're from Starlight Academy,
yet your stage changed upon going to perform.
I believe the system did some sort of spatial transferrance.
You mean that Aikatsu system did this?
Indeed.
I ran a scan of the facility earlier
and a bug was detected in the system.
Like a glitch?
I'd like to talk to you two about your circumstances.
Both machines malfunctioning at the same time caused a rift in time and space.
Two worlds that were never supposed to overlap merged together.
And in that rift, it would seem a special kind of place was created.
A rift containing two worlds?
Are we stuck here-pri?
Not to worry, the gates to both PriPara and Starlight Academy's worlds
haven't disappeared.
Everything will be fine.
Actually, you're able to come and go quite freely. I believe this is an entirely new area altogether.
A brand-new area!
Lots of idols could gather here!
You could say it's an idol paradise!
What about the school?
What should we do about the shows scheduled after this?
That's the question... Everyone was looking forward to those.
May I offer my opinion?
The floor is yours.
Alright. We'll meet in the room over there. Right this way.
Now then, they'll be a while, so feel free to talk amongst yourselves.
So, Akari!
I wanna hear all about Starlight Academy!
You bet!
And I'd love to learn all about PriPara!
You've got it!
Capisce!
What's up!
I'm Shinjou Hinaki!
Your pop fit slays!
Thanks-pri!
I'm Mirei! With a pop and a step, I've gotcha!
Your bangs and hairclip are just adorbs-pri!
Thank you!
Hello there.
I'm Sophy.
And I'm Hikami Sumire.
Pleased to meet you.
Dancing freely on stage
The red rose of passion,
Kurebayashi Juri!
Always in top form
and ready to strike first!
I'm Toudou Sion!
Mucho gusto! Or should I say, pleased to meet you.
Go. Well met.
Whoa! Are you two twins?
You two are so lovely!
Oh, I know right?
You guys are pretty cute, too.
But you're nothing compared to me and Reona.
D-Dorothy! That's rude!
Nice to meet you.
I'm the girl who dances like lightning,
Kurosawa Rin!
And I'm Amahane Madoka!
Super cool to meet you!
Guess they're not too shabby...
There's so many girls here!
Plenty of demonic servants to be found!
This is so fun-garu!
So freakin' cute!
You're really great with goats!
She's my friend, after all.
I'm the cheerful idol,
Doujima Niina!
Nice to meet ya!
I'm Falulu!
All of them are the same...
What a strange place...
That's the system!
PriPara ding-dong...
We have an announcement regarding the status of the performances
please gather around the stage.
We've come to a decision regarding the planned shows.
Though things may have started off with some unexpected issues,
it's wonderful that idols from two different idol agencies,
Starlight Academy and PriPara,
could meet and form bonds with one another.
Because of this,
we've decided hold a joint [dunno what to do with live fest]
That sounds like fun!
Yeah!
Singing, dancing, and freedom, baby!
Bring along whoever you want to sing with you
and give everyone a performance to remember!
Also,
we can directly transmit any song into your head,
so no need to worry if you don't already know the lyrics.
Hop to it! The early bird gets the worm!
Who's going to be our first singer?
Me!
The idol of all idols;
in other words, me!
The center of the universe...
Kokoneー
Me, Dorothy!
It's gotta be the most charming person in the whole world first, don'tcha think?
Hold it right there! You can't just interrupt me like that!
Miyabi and I were going to sing first!
I already called dibs!
No way, it's me!
Nom me!
That's quite enough, Kokone.
That's a little selfish of you.
I agree. You're causing quite a fuss.
Such grace and insight...
Are you a martial artist?
Indeed.
I know some Naginata.
I'd like to see such an extraordinary skill myself.
Let us do battle!
I would love to engage you.
Very well. I accept.
What?
Then let's take this elsewhere.
Of couirse.
Um, Sion? We got a performance to do!
Miyabi, what about singing with me?
How about the two of us go then-pri?
I'd love to!
Dreams times effort, multiplied by friendship times friendship
Let's marble mix it up! Off to paradise, here we go!
We don't even know the rules
A miracle that'll make you do a double-take
Just a couple of mixed up idols
and a dream of Divine idolhood!
An unstoppable beat
We're not quite natural
but not quite dolled up
Let's get a little girly!
Wearing a smile on our eyelids
po-po-n
On my way to a brand new me
Dreams times effort
Cyalume change!
Our voices multiplied by never giving up
Heart-pounding and thrilling, time to marble mix it uo!
I'm not alone 'cause I'm with you
It's not just anybody, it's you
A mysteriously magical future paradox!
Marble!
Ahaha!
What a lovely show.
You two totally killed it up there!
Thanks a bunch-pri!
I think I'd like to give performing a try, too.
The stage is all yours. Be my guest.
I bet everyone would love to hear your rendition of Tutu Ballerina!
What kind of song is that?
It's a super aloof but stylish song!
If you want someone who can pull off the whole icy cold vibe, then look no further than Sophy!
Pshuu...
Really?
She seemed pretty amicable to me...
Aha!
Aroma!
Thou art demon kin!
Wouldst thou join us in subjugating this realm?
Pardon?
I'm a demon?
It's no use hiding. Thy cards give thee away.
Thy art a vampire, predicting armageddon with thy cursed cards!
I guess the designers could be a little demonic...
You do also enjoy fortune telling...
Join us and subjugate the world!
I appreciate the offer, but I'd like to just perform...
She's out of control-pri...
I'd say this calls for a Red Flash-pri!
A pickled plum?
That's quite enough.
Are you prepared, my little cagebirds?
Let us make for the stage!
Alright!
Okay.
Let's go!
We'll share our thanks with you!
For all the time we've walked together side-by-side
The amount of wonderful stories we have will continue growing
Special Appeal! Making Drama!
We'll keep having miraculous meetings!
We'll shine forever
in our idol paradise
Our pretty activities will never end!
I love it!
Hey, Sion!
Miyabi, come on!
I thought we could sing together...
Those look like they're made out of super delicious candy!
It looks so cute but so munchable-garu!
I know, right?
There's lot of sweets in the lyrics, too.
I bet the clothes and the song taste amazing-garu!
I wanna sing my heart out!
Then how about we sing together!
Oh, lemme sing with ya!
Bright and sunny sweets, the occasional chocolate
Take a bit of the decorations and you'll be delighted
A secret, but the girls know it
Sweets are happy clothes, wouldn't you say
(Mysterious) A pleasant flavor
(Special) Gentle and happy
A little sweet magic's gonna make your heart skip a beat
Caramelizing your heart kinda like having your first crush
Pastel colored macarons that make you dance with delight
What a surprise, ah!
Then your cheeks, ooh!
The joy spreading through your heart like souffle chiffon
The power to make everyone become friends
So wonderful. ah!
Heart-pounding, ooh!
A sweet tale
How long're you gonna do this?!
Everybody keeps beating us to the punch!
Say,
Would you like to sing with me?
Nono!
Risa!
We'd love to!
A brand new day has dawned
Good morning, lay hee! It's time to wake up!
Over all the hills and even through the woods,
Take a deep breath and relax
Give all your worries the flick
(Gently, softly)
and leave them out to air atop a tree
and bid them goodbye, hey!
Lively, energetic and full of life
Happy as happy can be, we sing gently with a ho ho ho.
And friendly,
as close as two friends can be!
Hey little goat! (Baa baa baa) Hey little bird! (Tweet tweet tweet)
So come join this song, lay hee!
Cyalume change!
Hey little pig! (oink oink oink) Hey, horses and cows! (Neigh, moo)
Hey little frog! (Ribbit ribbit) Hey little duck! (quack quack)
And hello to you, too! (heigh ho!) Come join us, everyone!
Lively, energetic and full of life
Happy as happy can be, we sing gently with a ho ho ho.
And friendly,
as close as two friends can be!
Come join this song, lay hee!
Pick up your feet, raise your voice, and come join this song, lay hee!
It's about time
for me
to make my appearance!
Gracias...
In other words,
thank you.
De nada, señorita
You're most welcome, mademoiselle.
Won't you rise with me
to zeal's stage?
You've the scent of a prodigy,
and even better,
you don't have one of those preposterous sentence-enders.
I accept.
Can you feel it?
The blazing flame of revolution
ignited by the Shikyouin Hibiki!
You there, within that powerful yet weak-willed heart of yours,
find yourself spurred by revolution
You there, heed now the future assured by my unerring nobility
And leave the past behind
Unsuited to such things as ladylike apparel or lipstick
I am envied by god and mortal alike,
for I am a Perfect Knight of Beauty
Pure Amore Love
Let it bloom ever magnificently
A casablanca bursting open like raging magma
Amore, come here,
I shall tell you now the truth
What is “love”?
Love is merely a fantasy for fools.
Yet it is by the whims of love
that we two have been drawn here
Cyalume Change!
Amore, ah!
Avert not your eyes from the flower;
its hue rivaling any shade of crimson
This pristine frenzy is for you
Indeed, it’s for the sake of love
and these dreams that “I” am here
Juri, you were amazing!
But what should we do...
Vanilla Chili Pepper's song is meant for three people...
That footwork...
Her swordsmanship is amazing, too...
That was an excellent rehearsal.
You have my sincerest gratitude.
I thank you as well.
I'll look forward to facing off with you one day.
Excuse me, Sion!
Would you like to perform with us?
Opportunity only knocks once.
I'd be glad to.
Aren'tcha forgetting someone over here?
Bright and blinding, haa..
Dancing to the sun's rhythm, we dance and sing "Ole"
Different rhythmic stomps join together in unison
Everyone's got things they love and things they don't
No two people in the world are exactly alike, turning like the colors in a kaleidoscope
Now come here
and feel, feel, feel the energy
Just make a move
Give into the impulse and clap, clap, clap your hands
one, two, three
Step, step, step let it resonate
Our miracle is just beginning
Dreams and aspirations are one in the same
giving birth to a neww dream
Dance to your heart's content, chicas
Our future is right around the corner
Right now no one knows
the sound of a melody yet to be heard
But when we dance together,
we can bring to future to us
Bright and blinding, ah..
Ugh, that's it!
Reona and I are definitely going next, or you're gonna hear it from me!
If you say so, Dorothy.
PriPara ding-dong...
It's about 6 PM. The area will soon be closing.
Seriously?!
We agreed upon doing things by the PriPara system's rules,
so no one is permitted to be here past 6 PM.
We hate to disappoint everyone.
It's over already...
I really wanted to sing more...
But in better news,
whenever you visit this space,
it may very well be possible to vist each other's worlds.
This how we found each other,
so let's take the time to get to know each other.
Okay!
Yeah!
You can put on even more joint shows tomorrow!
See you
tomorrow!
Hey, you all!
See you tomorrow!
Have a good day-pri!
You all too!
See you later!
Looking forward to tomorrow!
Well, see you tomorrow!
Take care!
Right back at'cha!
Wait, what?
My dorm
is usually here, isn't it?
What?!
Akari!
Sumire, Hinaki...
Have you seen what they're saying online?
"The celebrity idol, Hoshimiya Ichigo
changed her name to Hoshimiya Pineapple"...
Pineapple?!
It's not that it's not cute, but...
I just can't picture that!
Next up in the news...
The idol group, Dancing Divas, have just announced they'll be disbanding.
They've said they'll be debuting as a group of treasure hunters from now on.
I-Impossible...
I'm not an actress in Aikatsu Teacher
but It's not a school teacher, either...
Now I'm a stageplay teacher?!
I'm home!
This is my house, right?
This is supposed to be an Italian restaurant!
Oh Big Sis, you're back.
Oh, Non!
Wh...
Huh?
You're a boy?
But, you called me "big sis"
so you must be Non, right?
What's gotten into you?
It's really me. Your brother, Nonsuke.
"Nonsuke"?!
Wh-Where did all these animals come from?!
Do you think they're the mascots?
Did something happen?
Our monja sign changed?!
Why's it "Monja Ninja" instead of "Ninja Monja"?!
I guess it's not that different...
Laala!
Akari!
There's something weird about the real world!
You guys had weird thing happen, too?
I wonder...
It looks like this fusion has been affecting things in the outside world, too.
We're all rather worried.
We just wonder what's going on.
But, why man? What's going on?
Upon doing some investigating, we uncovered a very significant fact.
Our two worlds connected,
and this fused space was created.
As a result, a fork in the space-time continuum appeared.
A fork in the space-time continuum?
That's right.
A fork path in the flow of time was created.
You've broken from the path in the flow of time you were supposed to follow,
and entered a different flow altogether.
Now new forks keep appearing,
and this space encounters new branches each time.
We've also discovered it's possible to jump to other parts of the path.
What do you mean?
Does that mean we'll keep getting sent to other strange worlds?
Yes.
We'll run into the next brance after three days.
But we've calculated the next one after that
will be 100 million years from now.
That long?!
I can't even begin to image what that'd be like-pri!
So our original worlds will only continue to get farther away...
So we'll never be able to return to our original worlds and see the people from them?
But my friends and family aren't here...
And the fans who cheer us on...
Um, is there anything we can do?
This is merely conjecture,
but if we were somehow able to jump back to the first point of divergence
it may be possible for us to return to the original timeline.
Is that even possible?
That I cannot say for certain.
However, the power which creates and sustains this space
is idols' radiance.
If we were to be able to combine that radiance, we could bring about a miracle.
An idol's...
radiance...
But how do we combine it?
Come on!
That's easy-peasy.
We just gotta put on a buncha shows!
Don't ya think we'd shine really bright then?
Yeah!
Agreed!
I've been wanting to perform more anyways!
If we recruit our friends and sing the songs we like,
there's a lot we can sing-pri!
I'm so hyped!
I think it's only fair if Reona and I go first.
If you say so, Dorothy.
Let us sing with you, too!
Then let's go!
Get hyped to the max!
And relax!
Ultra maxxed!
Hey, everybody! We're gonna get everything back to normal in no time!
You and me and a happy smiling shining happy train
Yeah, mega lucky super sparkly lucky train
Come on! Adventure's just around the corner
oh, my lucky tain!
You're Cinderella, and the clock's struck midnight
(too bad(
You want everyone to remember
(let's dance!)
Bid yourself from that night "goodbye"
Cuz tomorrow's back to normal
You're just an unpolished gem
you just have to keep polishing yourself
Countless hours passing by
Come on, it's your super shiny, ultra sparkly lucky time
Make a wish upon a shooting star before it passes you by
so you can once again board that ultra cheerful happy train
Maybe sometimes you'll slip up
but that might lead you to your treasure
Oh my happy train
Heart-pounding and thrilling -- oh my lucky train!
A small wormhole has appeared in the sky.
10-4.
Let's keep up that momentum.
Let's go, Madoka!
Alright!
Take a step forward and ring the bell of blessings
and take a bite from this sweet, red apple
With just one bite,
you've already become our captive
Kneel there before me
My soul
twinges with unsatiable thirst
We call out your name
and invite you somewhere beyond fate
Reversible Ring
where darkness and light intermix
A moebius strip wrapped around your finger
The captivating demon and the smiling angel
Cyalume change!
Remember we two maidens
Reversible-Ring
A moebius strip wrapped around your finger
Fear not
and yield yourself to us
The Devil ＆ Angel;
Worship we two maidens
An idol's radiance;
for that, you need look no further than us.
My heart beats to the rhythm of this magic ornamentation
and I come alive with joy
Love and dates -- it's all so boring
Tonight, too, I want to dance
My heart comes alight like raging fire
The ttrobbing passion in my heart has no end
May this flower rooted deep inside my heart come into bloom
I'll shine even brighter than ever before
I'll bloom just as beautifully with the fire lit inside of me
Just like the red passion flowers
The flowers of my dream bloom splendidly
Should these flower petals ever wither,
They'll return as buds once again
Just like the red passion flowers
It's about time we go on.
Next up: the Kansai team!
Let's give'em a good show!
Halt, I beseech of you!
The cauldron of hell hath been opened.
This is the beginning of the demons' night!
It's finally our turn to sing and stuff!
Gaarmageddon's show-garu!
Then how about all 6 of us sing?
Team Sekimageddon-garu!
The unspoken words hiding inside your heart,
Set them free and raise your voice
Be the brightest version of yourself
and take hold of all the things you love
Winners and losers don't matter
Come let's join hands
Hey jimp! The part's just getting started!
Hey! Let's go, it's party time!
Let's dance with 1,2,3! Into the future! We're together forever
We're never ever going to give up, we swear on that
LEt's sing "I'll do my best"! Tomorrow will be even brighter
Cyalume Change!
Muster up your courage and search for joy
and take over PriPara!
LEt's sing "I'll do my best"! Tomorrow will be even brighter
Muster up your courage and search for joy
and take over PriPara!
They've also produced radiance!
We're so close to a miracle-pri!
The light faded...
The wormhole in the sky has disappeared.
I suppose it's no use.
But why...
It seems we'll need more power if we're going to move this space...
But can we even produce enough...
What's with all this?!
We've been performing day in and day out the whole time!
How many times is it gonna take before it's enough?!
After three days, it's gonna take 100 million years worth of power isn't it?!
Can we even really bring about a miracle?
Will we ever be able to go back to normal?
It'll be okay!
We can make a miracle happen!
I know we can! No matter how much work it takes!
Yeah!
I'm with Laala! We can do this!
I mean, we almost did it!
Akari?
We were all just strangers who'd never met until yesterday.
But this is how we met!
And we've been doing so many wonderful shows!
You know, when I first met you, I was really surprised!
But when we ended up performing together, I had so much fun!
Same here!
It really felt like the start of something new!
Laala...
Akari!
Laala!
Let's sing together!
Please scan the appropriate amount of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord Change Start!
The pink checks and layers are simply stunning!
Just like the Starlight Academy Marching Coord
Pink Parade Coord
Even in another world, the feeling stays the same!
The cute ribbons tie your memories together!
Twinkle Ribbon Cyalume Coord!
Stop trying to be like all those other girls you see
You're better off just being yourself
If you feel the spark in your heart,
come search for your ideals
Every single memory we've made,
we'll snap'em in half
and complete the set with our friends!
Make it! Once you get started, you're invicible!
Make up! Headed towards a radiant future
Making Drama, switch on!
That dream's not just a dream anymore
You can dance!
Anyone can be anything!
You can walk the runway!
Sing a song!
Let's make a miracle!
Cyalume Change!
MAke it! Giving up on that dream is just not in the cards!
Make up!
Make it! Once you get started, you're invicible!
Make up! Headed towards a radiant future
Your dream's not just a dream anymore
Anyone can be anything!
PriPara PriPara-dise
Laala! Akari!
You guys!
Something about the show you just did really lifted our spirits!
It makes me believe we can pull off a miracle.
Indeed! You're laser focused.
We'll have to give gathering the idols radiance another go.
Laser focused?
Actually, I've been thinking...
we've been doing all these thrown together performances, but what if instead,
we prepared for one big, best of the best performance intsead?
All of together for the best performance ever?
So you're saying we should all work together for one big show-pri?
That sounds so fun-garu!
We could have the people who perform on stage and the people who support from the audience.
We'd be bringing all our radiance together as one.
That certainly sounds like an idea worth trying.
In that case, we'll hold the show after three days.
Otherwise that's our last chance for another 100 million years.
But who should we choose?
Obviously it's--
me!
Wouldn't Laala and Akari be good choices?
You're right.
They were the first of us to meet.
Okay!
Miss Akari and Miss Laala will be the centers
in a brand new idol group!
Then it's gotta be
the ones who had a smash hit concert! The super idols, Luminas!
And the team who emerged victorious at the Divine Idol Grand Prix: SoLaMi Smile!
The new team will be made of these six members!
They're SoLaMi Luminas!
Garu!
Tch. Fine, whatever.
If it's support we must play, then I suppose we'll just have to do it.
So then what are the supporters supposed to do-garu?
Hm...
We could create a new ultimate special appeal...
And then we can create a new Making Drama!
Why don't we work on it together?
A Making Drama and Special Appeal put together... I like the sound of that!
It's a Special Making Drama Appeal!
Aha. That's a bit long.
How about Making Appeal!
That sounds great!
If Kiriya was here, she'd say "isn't this chill?"
If Ms. Ajimi was here, she'd say
"
That settles it.
The six members of SoLaMi Luminas will prepare to take the stage.
Everyone else should put forth maximum effort to support them.
Okay!
The three of us will work on putting together the best song for the show.
Yeah! Let's get amped!
We'll be doing everything we can to support you.
Stylish!
Amazing!
Collaboration!
Yeah!
Isn't there one more thing you need?
Tsubasa!
Cosmo!
The best performance deserves the best outfits, right?
We've got this cosmic covered.
Laala and her friends should be here any minute now!
I'm looking forward to practicing with them!
Akari!
Oh!
Laala!
Nice to see you!
Oh, Sophy?
I'm down here!
How's it going? Capisce!
Huh? That's you, Laala?!
So you really are a primary schooler...
Then does that mean...
You're Mirei?
Is it really that surprisng...
pri?
I can't believe it!
Thanks for having us today.
Of course!
You good with doing our regular old training?
Yeah, that's totally okay!
Ai-katsu, ai-katsu, ai-katsu
Their stamina is unbeatable.
We're going to have to work overtime if we want to catch up.
We're not gonna fall behind!
Pri! Para! Pri! Para!
Wait for me!
Ai-katsu!
Rock climbing...
If this is what the Starlight Academy students are doing,
then it's no wonder their idol abilities are on another level.
Just a little longer! Hang in there!
C-Capisce!
Pshuu...
Oh no! Sophy got blown away!
The center of the universe...
Kokone!
I think ya mean me!
No, me!
They just can't get their act together.
But despite that, we've been making good prgoress.
Yeah! This is looking to be one awesome Making Appeal!
It's chock full of idols' radiance!
Are we sure we can pull this off?
We only have one chance...
That's quite true.
If it doesn't end up being the best concert anyone's ever seen,
it'll be a big failure.
Hearing that gives me anxiety!
It still feels like something's missing...
Yeah, but thwat...
Headmistress, we have a problem!
Whatever is the matter, Johnny?
When we were meeting about the new song, I heard from MegaBro —
"MegaBro"?
Oh, you mean Meganii?
Yeah!
I found out something that was totally shocking!
No way!
The next performance will be the last one?!
Darn straight.
Er, yes.
The power of our idols will return things to normal,
and the two worlds will separate.
We'll be cut off from each other forever.
So after that, we won't be able to meet up any more?
Yeah.
To make matters worse, all of our memories of this will disappear too.
I see. So we'll forget all about this wonderful meeting...
How unfortunate...
Yes...
I should tell Oozora and the others,
I just hope it doesn't make them hesitant to go on...
Well, about that...
You've already told everyone?!
Indeed.
I had the opportunity to gether everyone earlier.
So how did they take the news?
This is their final performance.
They're not going to be able to do things together anymore.
Everyone was shocked at first, of course.
But it wasn't long before they shifted and said,
Who decided that?
If it'll take a miracle to turn our worlds back, then we'll just make another miracle so we can meet again!
We've made miracles before and we can do it again!
"We'll give it our everything.
"
We have to place our faith in our radiance.
After all,
we're idols!
We should place our hopes in them, too.
I know those girls can bring about a miracle.
Ai-katsu! Ai-katsu!
So this is PriPara!
Everything here is so cool!
You could come here every day!
And look at all those animals!
Pri-Para! Pri-Para!
Oh, Laala. You're as lively as ever!
Something about being in idol in PriPara
increases my power by 100 times!
Your idol aura's increased 100 times over, too!
That's the power of PriPara-pri!
You're far too slow, my little cagebirds!
Holy moly!
And that's the power of pickled plums-pri.
Hologrammation!
We used the power of hologrammation to construct a 3000 meter rock wall.
What?!
Ai-katsu!
This is the first I've ever
climbed a rock wall this tall.
PriPara is something else.
This is my winning idiot power!
With the power of both effort and calculations, we can't be beat!
Ai-katsu!
Pri-Para!
Pri...
Ah, I give up! I'm out of ideas!
Then a change of pace is in order.
At times like this, it's best to get up and moving.
What's all this?
Wow, it's so lovely!
After that conversation, we all thought there must be some way we can pitch in!
We want the stage itself to be able to give off the brightest shine!
This is our aikatsu!
This is our way to say "we're all idols"!
It's like everyone's [whatever word I used before]
has come together!/united
Excelente!
In other words, fantastic!
It's time for us to pull ourselves together.
Yeah!
Let's climb together!
Okay!
Each and every one of us shines in our own way.
And when we bring all of our [word I used] together,
I know we'll put on the greatets show ever!
Whatcha guys lollygagging around for?
Have you all forgotten about the Making Appeal?
Has hell's banquet not started?
Alright. Let's go wrap things up.
Yeah!
We finally made it...
The sky looks stunning...
I hope everything works out tomorrow...
We won't know until we try-pri.
All we can do is give it our all.
Mhm.
Let's have fun and go all out!
Capisce!
Whoa!
We call it the "Star Paradise Coord".
Looking forward to working with you, partner.
Get out there and show us the greatest show ever.
We'll cosmically be cheering for you from the sidelines.
Thank you!
Look up at the sky and smile
The ones who twinkle and shine,
we're SoLaMi Luminas!
Pretty!
A surprise-pri?
How wonderful!
This rocks!
Thank you, everyone!
We're gonna have the best time ever, so let's get hyped!
When our two worlds met, I got to sing with you
A miracle we found by chasing swinging notes
Our final, destined stage
The impossible is now possible, and we're so excited
Altogether now! Let's take a dive into this play!
Let me feel even more of your Appeal
I'm sure we share the same motivation to do our best!
Passing through us, connecting us, I'm so glad we can shine like this
Because we're idols! Yeah!
Singing the melody that was made when we met
Can you hear the sound of our racing hearts?
we'll bring our voices together, uniting our glimmer as one
Nature and happy tuning is what makes the sound of life
You know it well -- this lyric starts it all
We're making miracles on this very stage
Our voices reached them!
We're all friends, we're all idols!
Let's make this miracle happen-pri!
Our feelings...
Our defiant, inspiring steps
We should share those with them!
One single step leads to infinite possibilities!
Look at everyone's cards!
Give it your all and show how much you want it!
We should all work together! Allow us to join!
These are PriTickets
and Aikatsu cards!
Give it your all and show how much you want it!
For an idol, this is just the symbol of a new meeting
Never lose your faith in everyone's courage
They've been making miracles since the moment they met
and now they'll be shining at the brightest they've ever been in this finale!
One day you'll find yourself casually humming this tune
Don't ever forget the fun we had while we were together
It's almost time for the climax!
Get hyped to the max and go!
Singing the melody that was made when we met
we'll bring our voices together, uniting our glimmer as one
And the rhythm of our beating hearts comes together
With our smiles and happy tuning, let's create the best moment ever
Thank you. These lyrics will last forver
Let's sing this treasure
Ah, miracles are right within our grasp!
Making Appeal, switch on!
Friends
Fans
coords
Dreams
memories
the future
We can't be thankful enough!
The miraculous meeting!
An idol paradise for you!
This is
the idols' radiance!
Success! Your chance is starting!
Laala!
Yeah! Let's snap!
This isn't goodbye,
it's just goodbye until next time.
Yeah! Let's snap!
I know we'll meet again,
so
Wha?
It's already evening?
Wans't I supposed to perform today?
I wonder what happened...
It's over, isn't it?
But I don't remember a thing...
Ah.
This is...
Huh?
Today's supposed to be a special show...
What're you talking about-pri?
The show's been over for a while...
Pri?
Hm?
This isn't goodbye,
it's just goodbye until next time.
I know we'll meet again,
so
see you then!
We'll meet again! It's a promise!
A message you'll remember even after 10,000 years;
I'll share it with you!
My precious friends!
The fact we met means we were meant to be together
We can hear each other's songs
like we're singing in unison
Place all of your goals into the cards and put your dreams into the ticket
Carry friends
We'll meet again, but it feels like we won't have to wait
When do you want to meet next?
We'll have so much fun
We'll be together forever
Our wonderful story -- let's start something new
Pa-Pa-Ra Make it, Now!
Du-Du-Wa DO IT, Now!!
Singing is how we understand each other!
Our show will never end
Our Pretty Activites will continue forever
Even just one second
We'll meet each other wearing the best coord sever
We won't be able to stop compliment each other
We've gone back to our homes, but we can never talk enough!
Whether the present
Can't wait to see what's coming
in the future
(Our Dream Stage!)
We're the same generation, so let it resonate
Like a prism
shining is so many colors
It might sometimes feel lonely
but this promise is something we'll cherish
So now when your heart beats
look forward to it!